Finding Aid for Program in Comparative Study of Social Transformations (University of Michigan) records, 1987-2001
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Program in Comparative Study of Social Transformations (University of Michigan) records
1987-2001
1987-1997
University of Michigan. Program in Comparative Study of Social Transformations.
2011120 Bimu 2
An interdisciplinary research program at the University of Michigan, Comparative Study of Social Transformations (CSST) studied theoretical categories and questions around social change within past and present societies. Records include a complete run of the working papers, a collection of flyers and presentation papers from CSST sponsored colloquiums and faculty seminars, posters, and two video cassettes. Included within the working papers are both the original grant proposal for the funding of the CSST and working paper #21, "Taking Stock: The First Year of CSST," February 1989.
2 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The CSST records were received from the CSST program (donor no. 9931 ) in 2007.
No further additions to the records expected.
The collection is open without restriction.
Typewritten copies of working papers are included in the Bentley's collection. PDF versions were deposited in Deep Blue, the University of Michigan's Institutional Repository as part of the Center for Research on Social Organization collection. Links to the Deep Blue copies are provided in the item list below.
Sparked by great intellectual shifts of the late 1960s and 1970s, the CSST formed to better foster cross-discipline exchange across the fields of history, anthropology, and sociology. Each discipline had begun to borrow theories and practices from the others, but the borrowing did not constitute a complete exchange. In 1987 CSST was created as a grant proposal to the Presidential Initiatives Fund. The proposal, published as Working Paper #1 states, "We believe that the fields have in fact been converging on a common problematic, which might be stated as follows: How do groups of actors constituted and constrained by social and cultural structures act so as to transform the very structures that constituted them?" (p. 7). To most effectively tackle this question, the CSST proposed a series of graduate and faculty seminars as well as a series of public lectures from visiting scholars to focus on core themes through the year. The first year update, published as working paper 21, February 1989, indicated cross-discipline exchange provoked productive discussions and the proposed agenda gradually morphed to accommodate faculty and student interests. CSST was initially housed within the Center for Research on Social Organizations.
Initially proposed as an exchange between three disciplines, the CSST by the mid-1990s, had grown to include over 150 faculty affiliates and scholars from a large cross section of disciplines. Disciplines represented included African-American and African Studies, American Culture, Anthropology, Architecture and Urban Planning, Art History, Asian Languages and Cultures, Business Administration, Chinese Studies, Communication Studies, Comparative Literature, Education, European Studies, English Studies, Film and Video, German Studies, History, Japanese Studies, Korean Studies, Latin American and Caribbean Studies, Law, Middle Eastern and North African Studies, Near Eastern Studies, Political Science, Philosophy, Psychology, Public Health, Romance Languages, Russian and Eastern European Studies, Sociology, and Women's Studies.
Throughout is history, the CSST fostered a national and international body of scholars focused on the need to develop new theoretical categories and questions around social change. A core theme was an examination of how existing forms of knowledge are socially and culturally founded and how these understandings are related to change and stability within past and present societies. Additionally, the CSST encouraged a deep consideration of the ways language shapes human interactions, particularly how sets of categories are socially produced and policed.
The CSST was dissolved in the mid-2000s and much of the program's operations were absorbed by the Department of History.
The records for Comparative Study of Social Transformations (CSST) contain a complete run of CSST working papers, Speaker Series flyers and presentation papers, photographs, and three video cassettes from the Dean's Lecture Series. The materials are organized into three series: Speaker Series, Working Papers, and AV Materials.
Subjects:
Organizational sociology.; Social sciences--Study and teaching.; Center for Research on Social Organization.; University of Michigan. Program in Comparative Studies of Social Transformations.; Carby, Hazel V.; Prashad, Vijay.
Contributors:
Carby, Hazel V.; Prashad, Vijay.
Genre Terms:
Videotapes.
- Speaker Series, 1995-1999
  Speaker Series, 1995-1999 (0.75 linear feet), includes flyers and copies of presented papers primarily given at the Faculty Seminars hosted by the CSST. Visiting scholars pre-circulated papers, optimizing discussion and exchange during the two-hour sessions. Visiting scholars included Dipesh Chakrabarty, Alex Own, Kay Warren, and Robin D. G. Kelley.
  - Flyers, 1996-1999 (Box 1)
  - Posters, 1990-1998 (Box 1)
  - Warren, Kay "Reading History as Resistance: Mayan Public Intellectuals in Guatemala,", December 7, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Honig, Bonnie, "Political Theory and the Displacement of Politics,", November 16, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Ellison, Julie, "A Short History of Liberal Guilt,", February 1, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Stoler, Ann, "Genealogies of Racisms and Their Regimes of Truth,", February 25, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Van der Veer, Peter, "The Moral State: Religion, Nation and Empire in Victorian Britain and British India,", March 14, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Colás, Santiago, "Latin American Culture Studies, Marx, and Style,", March 28, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Rose, Sonya O., "Cultural Analysis and Moral Discourses: Episodes, Continuities, and Transformations,", October 3, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Stephens, Sharon, "Nationalism, Nuclear Policy, and Children in Cold War America,", April 10, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Procacci, Giovanna, "Omnes or Singulation? Citizenship as Government Strategies,", January 29, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Chakrabarty, Dipesh, "Witness to Suffering: Domestic Cruelty and the Birth of the Subject,", February 11, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Kelley, Robin D. G., "New Monastery: Thelonious Monk and the Jazz Avant-Garde,", February 25, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Amanda, "The Temptations of Aggrandized Agency: Feminist Histories and Cultural Analysis,", March 11, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Owen, Alex, "Magic and the Ambiguities of Modernity,", March 25, 1999 (Box 1)
- Working Papers, 1987-1997
  Working Papers, 1987-1997 (1.0 linear foot), include the complete run of published papers exploring evolving disciplinary boundaries and thought accompanying social transformations. The papers represent the diverse nature of the CSST, including national and international scholarship from disciplines including African American and African Studies, History, Cultural Studies, Business Administration, Literature, Communication Studies, Religious Studies, Political Science, Philosophy, Public Health, and Women's Studies.
  The CSST Working Papers were published as part of the CSST series as well as the Center for Research on Social Organizations (CRSO) Working papers series. Thus CSST #1 is also identified as CRSO #344. Digital copies of the working papers are also available in Deep Blue, the University of Michigan's Institutional Repository. A link to the Deep Blue copy of each paper is included in the item list below.
  - 1. William Sewell, Terrence McDonald, Sherry Ortner, and Jeffery Paige. "Program in the Comparative Study of Social Transformations," (CRSO #344), May 1987 (Box 1)
  - 2. William Sewell. "Labor History, Uneven Development, and the Autonomy of Politics: The Dockworkers of Nineteenth-Century Marseille," (CRSO #346) Subsequently published in American Historical Review 93.3 (1988): 604-637, July 1987 (Box 1)
  - 3. Jeffery Paige, "Coffee, Copper, and Class Conflict in Central America and Chile: A Critique of Zeith's Civil Wars in Chile and Zeldin and Radcliffe's Landlords and Capitalists," (CRSO #347), September 1988 (Box 1)
  - 4. Geoff Eley, "In Search of the Bourgeois Revolution: The Particularities of German History," (CRSO #357), September 1987 (Box 1)
  - 5. Terrence McDonald, "The Burdens of Urban History: The Theory of the State in Recent American Social History," (CRSO #355), May 1988 (Box 1)
  - 6. Mayer Zald, "History, Sociology, and Theories of Organization," (CRSO #357), May 1988 (Box 1)
  - 7. Maris Vinovskis, "Have Social Historians Lost the Civil War? Some Preliminary Demographic Speculations," (CRSO #358), May 1988 (Box 1)
  - 8. Jeffery Paige, "Revolution and the Agrarian Bourgeoisie in Nicaragua," (CRSO #363), October 1988 (Box 1)
  - 9. Ronal Suny, "Nationalism and Class as Factors in the Revolution of 1917" (CRSO #365), October 1988 (Box 1)
  - 10. Nicholas Dirks, "The Original Caste: Power, History, and Hierarchy in South Asia," (CRSO #368), October 1988 (Box 1)
  - 11. Nicholas Dirks, "The Invention of Caste: Civil Society in Colonial India," (CRSO #369), October 1988 (Box 1)
  - 12. Mayer Zald, "Sociology as a Discipline: Quasi-Science and Quasi-Humanities," (CRSO #369), October 1988 (Box 1)
  - 13. Michael Kennedy and Konrad Sadkowski, "Constraints on Professional Power in Soviet-Type Society: Insights from the Solidarity Period in Poland," (CRSO #371), November 1988 (Box 1)
  - 14. Martin Whyte, "Evolutionary Changes in Chinese Culture," (CRSO #372), November 1988 (Box 1)
  - 15. Karl Monsma, "World Market, Class Conflict, and Rural Coercion in Post-Colonial Buenos Aires," (CRSO #373), November 1988 (Box 1)
  - 16. Nicholas Dirks, "Ritual and Resistance: Subversion as a Social Fact," (CRSO #375), December 1988 (Box 1)
  - 17. Janise Hurtig, "Social Transformations of Gender in South America: A Working Annotated Bibliography," (CRSO #376), December 1988 (Box 1)
  - 18. Geoff Eley, "Labour History-Social History-Altagsgeschichte: Experience, Culture, and the Politics of the Everyday. A New Direction for Germany Social History?" (CRSO #378) Published in journal of Modern History 61 (1989): 297-343., January 1989 (Box 1)
  - 19. Renee Anspach, "Notes on the Sociology of Medical Discourse: The Language of Class Presentation," (CRSO #379), January 1989 (Box 1)
  - 20. Howard Kimeldorf, "World War Two and the Deradicalization. of American Labor: A 'Deviant Case' Study," (CRSO #383), February 1989 (Box 1)
  - 21. Geoff Eley, "Taking Stock: The First Year of CSST," (CRSO #385), February 1989 (Box 1)
  - 22. Silvia Pedraza-Bailey, "Immigration Research: A Conceptual Map," (CRSO #385, February 1989 (Box 1)
  - 23. Sherry Ortner, Nicholas Dirks, and Geoff Eley, "Culture/Power/History: Series Prospectus," (CRSO #386), March 1989 (Box 1)
  - 24. Sherry Ortner, "A Feminist Perspective on Christopher Lasch: 'The Social Invasion of the Self," (CRSO #387), April 1989 (Box 1)
  - 25. Akos Rona-Tas, "Does Rational Choice Have Utility on the Margins?" (CRSO #388), April 1989 (Box 1)
  - 26. Seong Nae Kim, Joanne Goodwin, Kathleen Canning, "Research Fellows Conference Panel on "The Politics of Social Transformation," (CRSO #389), June 1989 (Box 1)
  - 27. Anne Gorsuch and Sharon Reitman, Research Fellows Conference Panel on "Struggle, Conflict, and Constraints on Social Chance," (CRSO #390), June 1989
  - 28. Nilufer Isvan, Akos Rona-Tas, Cynthia Buckley, Theresa Deussen, and Mayfair Yang, Research Fellows Conference Panel on "Subordinate Actors and Their Marginalization in Social Theory," (CRSO #391), June 1989 (Box 1)
  - 29. William Sewell, Toward a Theory of Structure: Duality, Agency, and Transformation," (CRSO #392), June 1989 (Box 1)
  - 30. Peter Appelbaum, "The Power of Individual Subjectivity and the Subjectivity of Power in Education," (CRSO #396), July 1989 (Box 1)
  - 31. Nichola Beisel, "Family Ideology, Class Reproduction, and the Suppression of Obscenity in Nineteenth-Century New York," (CRSO #397), July 1989 (Box 1)
  - 32. Sherry Ortner, ed., "Author Meets Critics: Reactions to 'Theory in Anthropology Since the Sixties'," (CRSO #398), August 1989 (Box 1)
  - 33. Margaret Somers, "Does Social Theory Need History: Reflections on Epistemological Encounters 'in the Social Sciences," (CRSO #399), August 1989 (Box 1)
  - 34. William Sewell, "Gender, History, and Deconstruction: Joan Wallach Scott's Gender and the Politics of History," (CRSO #400), August 1989 (Box 1)
  - 35. Jeffrey Paige, "The Social Origins of Dictatorship, Democracy, and Socialist Revolution in Central America," (CRSO #405), September 1989 (Box 1)
  - 36. Cheryl Hyde, "Max Weber Meets Feminism: A Reconstruction of Charisma," (CRSO #407), September 1989 (Box 1)
  - 37. William Rosenberg, "Understanding Strikes in Revolutionary Russia," (CRSO #408), September 1989 (Box 1)
  - 38. Marjorie McCall-Sarbaugh. and Mayer Zald, "Child Labor Laws: A Historical Case of Public Policy Implementation," (CRSO #409), October 1989 (Box 1)
  - 39. Geoff Eley, "Putting German (and British) Liberalism into Context: Liberalism, Europe, and the Bourgeoisie, 1840-1914" (CRSO #411), November 1989 (Box 1)
  - 40. Howard Kimeldorf, "Bringing Unions Back In (Or, Why We Need a New Old Labor History)," (CRSO #414), February 1990 (Box 1)
  - 41. David Mayfield and Susan Thorne, "In Flight From Politics: Social History and Its Discontents," (CRSO #415), February 1990 (Box 1)
  - 42. Geoff Eley, "Nations, Politics, and Political Cultures: Placing Habermas in the Nineteenth Century," (CRSO #417), April 1990 (Box 1)
  - 43. Geoff Eley, "Reviewing the Socialist Tradition," (CRSO #418), April 1990 (Box 1)
  - 44. William Sewell, Rethinking Labor History: Toward a Post-Materialist Rhetoric (CRSO #421), May 1990 (Box 1)
  - 45. Michael Kennedy, "The Intelligentsia and the Constitution of Civil Societies and Post Communist Regimes in Hungary and Poland," (CRSO #425), July 1990 (Box 1)
  - 46. Michael Kennedy, "The Constitution of Critical Intellectuals: Polish Physicians, Peace Activists and Democratic Civil Society," (CRSO #419), April 1990 (Box 1)
  - 47. Karl Monsma, "Dominant Class and State-Making in a Peripheral Area: Argentina After Independence," (CRSO #429), August 1990 (Box 1)
  - 48. Michael Kennedy, "Eastern Europe's Lessons for Critical Intellectuals," (CRSO #430), August 1990 (Box 1)
  - 49. Michael Kennedy, "The Alternative in Eastern Europe at Century's Start: Brzozowski and Machalski on Intellectuals and Socialism," (CRSO #432), August 1990 (Box 1)
  - 50. William Sewell, "Collective Violence and Collective Loyalties in France: Why the French Revolution Made a Difference," (CRSO #432), August 1990 (Box 1)
  - 51. Michael Kennedy, "Transformations of Normative Foundations and Empirical Sociologies: Class, Stratification and Democracy *in Poland," (CRSO #433), September 1990 (Box 1)
  - 52. Terrence McDonald, "What We Talk About When We Talk About History: The Conversations of History and Sociology," (CRSO #442), October 1990 (Box 1)
  - 53. Nicholas Dirks, "Is Vice Versa? Historical Anthropologies and Anthropological Histories," (CRSO #443), October 1990 (Box 1)
  - 54. Margaret Somers, "Narrativity, Culture, and Causality: Toward a New Historical Epistemology or Where is Sociology After the Historic Turn?" (CRSO #444), October 1990 (Box 1)
  - 55. Geoff Eley, "Is All the World a Text? From Social History to the History of Society Two Decades Later," (CRSO #445), October 1990 (Box 1)
  - 56. Sherry Ortner, "Who Shapes the Text? Sherpas and Sahibs on Mount Everest," (CRSO #446), October 1990 (Box 1)
  - 57. Craig Calhoun, "What Social Theory Needs from History Now: Culture and Action as Problems for Historical Sociology," (CRSO #447), October 1990 (Box 1)
  - 58. William Sewell, "Three Temporalities: Toward a Sociology of the Event," (CRSO #448), October 1990 (Box 1)
  - 59. Rogers Smith, "The New Non-Science of Politics: On Turns to History in Political Science," (CRSO #450), October 1990 (Box 1)
  - 60. Renato Rosaldo, "Feeling History: Reflections on the Western Culture Controversy," (CRSO #450) http, October 1990 (Box 1)
  - 61. Joan Wallach Scott, "Historicizing Experience," (CRSO #451), October 1990 (Box 1)
  - 62. Robert Gordon, The Past as Authority and as Social Critic: Stabilizing and Destabilizing Functions of History in Legal Argument," (CRSO #452), October 1990 (Box 1)
  - 63. Steven Mullaney, "Discursive Forums, Cultural Practices: History and Anthropology in Literary Studies," (CRSO #453), October 1990 (Box 1)
  - 64. Ann Stoler, "Sexual Affronts and Racial Frontiers: National Identity, 'Mixed Bloods,' And the Cultural Genealogies of Europeans in Colonial Southeast Asia," (CRSO #454), May 1991 (Box 1)
  - 65. Janet Hart, "Cracking the Code: Allegory and Political Mobilization *in the Greek Resistance," (CRSO #455), June 1991 (Box 1)
  - 66. Sherry Ortner, "Narrativity in History, Culture, and Lives," (CRSO #457), September 1991 (Box 1)
  - 67. Michael Kennedy, "The End to Soviet-type Society and the Future of Post-Communism," (CRSO #458), October 1991 (Box 1)
  - 68. Margaret Somers, "Political Culture and the Public Sphere: Rethinking the Making of Citizenship," (CRSO #459), October 1991 (Box 2)
  - 69. Ronald Suny, "Proletarian Dictator in a Peasant Land: Stalin as Ruler," (CRSO #460), October 1991 (Box 2)
  - 70. Geoff Eley, "German History and the Contradictions of Modernity," (CRSO #463), February 1992 (Box 2)
  - 71. Sherry Ortner, "Resistance and Class Reproduction Among Middle Class Youth," (CRSO #468), April 1992 (Box 2)
  - 72. Ferando Coronil, "Beyond Occidentalism: Towards Post-Imperial Geo-historical Categories," (CRSO #468), May 1992 (Box 2)
  - 73. Laura Downs, "If 'Woman' Is just an Empty Category, Then Why am I Afraid to Walk Alone at Night? Feminism, Post-Structuralism, and the Problematic Politics of Identity," (CRSO #469), May 1992 (Box 2)
  - 74. Timothy Mitchell, "The Return of the State," (CRSO #470), May 1992 (Box 2)
  - 75. David Scobey, "Exterminating Gestures: On Linking the Coercive and Discursive Moments of Power," (CRSO #471), May 1992 (Box 2)
  - 76. Nancy Fraser and Linda Gordon, "Beyond Contract-versus-Charity, Toward participation and Provision: On the Concept of Social Citizenship," (CRSO #472), May 1992 (Box 2)
  - 77. Roger Rouse, "Power in Popular Culture," (CRSO #473), May 1992 (Box 2)
  - 78. Ann Stoler, "Children on the Imperial Divide: Sentiments and Citizenship in Colonial Southeast Asia," (Box 2)
  - (CRSO #474), May 1992
  - 79. Linda Gregerson, "Powers of Desire: Specularity and the Subject of the Tudor State," (CRSO #477), May 1992 (Box 2)
  - 80. Michael Kennedy, "Intellectuals, Intellectuality, and the Restructuring of Power After Modernity and Communism," (CRSO #476), May 1992 (Box 2)
  - 81. Keith Nield, "Foucault on Power: ... Politics from Behind ... Societies on the Diagonal," (CRSO #477), May 1992 (Box 2)
  - 82. Andrea Press, "Mass Media and Moral Discourse: Social Class and the Rhetoric of Abortion," (CRSO #478), May 1992 (Box 2)
  - 83. Kathleen Canning, "Contesting the Power of Categories: Discourse, Experience, and Feminist Resistance," (CRSO #479), May 1992 (Box 2)
  - 84. Fred Cooper, "The Dialectics of Decolonization: Nationalism and Labor Movements on Postwar Africa," (CRSO #480), May 1992 (Box 2)
  - 85. Alf Lfidtke, "Perpetrators, Accomplices, Victims: Further Reflections of Domination as Social Practice: (CRSO #481), May 1992 (Box 2)
  - 86. Frank Mort, "Consumer Cultures, Political Discourse and the Problem of Cultural Politics," (CRSO #482), May 1992 (Box 2)
  - 87. Margaret Somers, "Narrativity, Narrative Identity, and Social Action: Rethinking English Working-Class Formation," (CRSO #485), June 1992 (Box 2)
  - 88. Margaret Somers, "The Political Culture Concept: The Empirical Power of Conceptual Transformation," (CRSO #486), June 1992 (Box 2)
  - 89. Michael Kennedy and Pauline Gianoplus, "Entrepreneurs and Expertise: Making Post-Communist Capitalism in Poland," (CRSO #489), December 1992 (Box 2)
  - 90. Michael Kennedy and Nicolae Harsayi, "Between Utopia and Dystopia: The Liabilities of Nationalism in Eastern Europe," (CRSO #490), December 1992 (Box 2)
  - 91. Margaret Somers, "A People Without Social Relations is a People Without Property: Property, Relationality, and Social Networks in the Formation of Political Rights," (CRSO #497), April 1993 (Box 2)
  - 92. Michael Kennedy, "Historical Legacies and Civil Societies: Alternative Nations in Eastern Europe," (CRSO #497), April 1993 (Box 2)
  - 93. Michael Kennedy, "Sociology's Trajectory at Century's End: Smooth Extensions, Normalized Discontinuities, and Reflexive Turns," (CRSO #498), April 1993 (Box 2)
  - 94. Margaret Somers and Gloria Gibson, "Reclaiming the Epistemological 'Other': Narrative and the Social Constitution of Identity," (CRSO #499), June 1993 (Box 2)
  - 95. Michael Taussig, "Solomon's Temple, or Beware of Taxi Drivers," (CRSO #504), October 1993 (Box 2)
  - 96. Brinkley Messick, "Written Culture," (CRSO #505), October 1993 (Box 2)
  - 97. Gyanendra Pandey, "Modes of Writing History: Hindu History in India Today," (CRSO #506), October 1993 (Box 2)
  - 98. Marilyn Ivy, "Mourning the Japanese Thing," (CRSO #508), October 1993 (Box 2)
  - 99. John Pemberton, "Heaven Forbid! What Sort of Sign is This?" (CRSO #508), October 1993 (Box 2)
  - 100. [Withdrawn] (Box 2)
  - 101. E. Valentine Daniel, "Crushed Glass, or Is There a Counterpoint to Culture?" (CRSO #510), October 1993 (Box 2)
  - 102. Adela Pinch, "Rubber Bands and Old Ladies," (CRSO #511), October 1993 (Box 2)
  - 103. Robin D. G. Kelley, "Nihilists or Stylists? Black Urban Culture and the Predicament of Social Science," (CRSO #512), October 1993 (Box 2)
  - 104. Michelle Lamont, "Race, Class, and Symbolic Boundaries in France and the U.S.," (CRSO #513), October 1993 (Box 2)
  - 105. Marjorie Levinson, "Posthumous Critique," (CRSO #514), October 1993 (Box 2)
  - 106. Laura Kipnis, "Appreciating Pornography," (CRSO #515), October 1993 (Box 2)
  - 107. [Never submitted.] (Box 2)
  - 108. Ming Cheng Lo, "Crafting the Collective Identity: The Origin and Trans formation of Taiwanese Nationalism," (CRSO #518), November 1993 (Box 2)
  - 109. Mabel Brezin, The Dead are Equal: History Making, Moral Relativism, and the Rise of the New Italian Right," (CRSO #534), July 1996 (Box 2)
  - 110. Peter van der Veer, The Moral State: Religion, Nation and Empire in Victorian Britain and British India," (CRSO #535), July 1996 (Box 2)
  - 111. Vincente Rafael, "'Your Grief is Our Gossip': Overseas Filipinos and Other Spectral Presences," (CRSO #538), October 1996 (Box 2)
  - 112. Sonya Rose, "Cultural Analysis and Moral Discourses: Episodes, Continuities, and Transformations," (CRSO #539), October 1996 (Box 2)
  - 113. William E. Connolly, "Suffering justice, and the Politics of Becoming," (CRSO #540), October 1996 (Box 2)
  - 114. Peter Uwe Hohendahl, "From the Eclipse of Reason to Communicative Rationality," (CRSO #541), October 1996 (Box 2)
  - 115. Gyan Prakash, "Reason and its Postcolonial Doubling," (CRSO #542), October 1996 (Box 2)
  - 116. William Scheuerman, "Decisionism and Legal Indeterminacy: The Case of Carl Schmitt," (CRSO #543), October 1996 (Box 2)
  - 117. Nivedita Menon, "Rights, Bodies and the Law: Towards a Feminist Ethics of justice," (CRSO #544), October 1996 (Box 2)
  - 118. Kenneth Baynes, "Procedural Democracy and the Limits of Liberalism," (CRSO #545), October 1996 (Box 2)
  - 119. Wendy Brown, "Power Without Logic Without Marx," (CRSO #546), October 1996 (Box 2)